[Music]
welcome back hope you're having a good
morning uh so far the gift Nifty is
indicating that the start will be in the
red it's not uh as bad the implied
opening actually is not as bad as what
we've seen in the past couple of days
but let's see we are in a bit of a
corrective phase so don't be surprised
if we get a bit of a Down tick today as
well but let's start with some numbers
um Yash is joining in he's tracking IC
lum how did the numbers look good
morning Sonia so month after month this
particular quarter we've been telling
our viewers that the numbers were look
were looking like outperforming the
industry and that's what's happened in
the quarter 4 results as well as far as
net premium earned is concerned that for
the company grew by 177% now this is an
outperformance of about 400 basis points
when it comes to the industry average so
that's a good thing and it's not just
the premium growth which has come about
this time but operational performance
has also shown a very strong growth as
far as underwriting loss is concerned
that is down about 7 1.2% the loss has
come at about 232 CR versus 251 CR
importantly combined ratio the most
important matric that is lowered to
102.2 in Q4 versus
104.2 uh last year in the same quarter
the management has given a very strong
statement on combined ratio saying that
by next year fourth quarter they'll be
able to reduce it further by about 50
basis point so that will be very
positive for the stock and the company
the company's practically managed to
improve its underwriting performance
whereever there hasn't been a very
strong growth and in health it's
improved its growth as well so of course
a very balanced performance and strong
Q4 numbers for IC all right yes thanks
very much for that uh so we'll track the
stock as it opens up now Angel one is
the next one we were focused on with the
fourth quarter review vamshi's got that
vami hi morning welcome good morning
prashan the strong show from Angel 1 I
would say in the fourth quarter uh
Revenue saw an uptick of almost 28%
sequentially coming in at 1,360 odd cror
and this was largely driven uh by the
highest number of orders that the
company recorded at almost 47 crores
which is an uptick of almost 35%
sequentially not only that given the
highest number of orders the fee income
has also seen a surge of almost 31%
sequentially coming in at around 1,19
odd crores uh IA has grown by 33% and
that is because the growth in revenues
has outpaced that in expenses uh fees
and commission expenses were up 22%
while employee expenses were up 12%
sequentially now contrasted with the
revenue growth and fee income growth of
almost 28% and 31% sequentially and as a
result the margins have also improved
for the counter they've improved to
almost 39% as uh and in fact seen an
uptick of almost 150 basis points net
profit resultantly has come in nearly
31% higher standing at 340 grow so good
show from Angel one expect the stock to
open higher today and the stock has been
an underperformer year to date Angel 1
is down 18% and from its 52 week high
the stock is corrected 26% so can a
strong Q4 push up the stock and recover
some of the underperformance I'm
watching two other stocks one is Tata
Communications and the other one is just
style both on the back of their Q4
numbers so first on Tata communication
the companies reported a margin Miss and
a bit of a Miss on the top line too
margins have fallen by 160 basis points
on a quarter- on quarter basis and more
than 400 basis points on a year-on-year
basis the reason for the margins coming
under pressure is because a company had
recently acquired not so recently a
couple of months back they had made two
Acquisitions kyera and switch and those
are reporting Abida losses uh so margin
misses what can hurt data communication
even on the top line the revenue growth
is just 1% on a sequential basis just
Style on the other hand has reported a
good quarter a revenue growth of 16%
year year margins have expanded to a
4year high at 26.1% there you have that
margin trajectory on just di profits
have gone up 25% year on year and this
is a company which is sitting on cash of
more than 4,600 crws okay thanks for
that well let's move across to the real
estate space we have some updates coming
in from suc realy and rade Enterprises
sonal is here to give us the latest on
that sonal hi good morning good morning
Sonia well operational updates are still
coming in let me start with Brigade
Enterprises it was the best quarterly SA
sales for the company and in terms of
yearly sales as well it was the best
ever year on a quarter 4 basis pre-sales
are up 53% to come at 2243 CR rupees
volumes are up 18% and the company says
they have a strong pipeline in terms of
launches as well around 12.6 million squ
ft² in their residential segment 6.33
million squ ft² in commercial and 1.06
million squ ft in their Hospitality
segment for santech as well pre-sales
growth was strong up 26% and this growth
has come in after quarters of decline
that we have seen and that's why I'm
going with green on sentech collections
however were down 32% the company says
they added seven large projects in the
Mumbai region with a gross development
value of 30,000 CR rupees which should
see pre-sales coming in in the next
financial year thank you for that moving
on to Ika for moreon biocon and jublin
fova Ika well I'll start with biocon
because after their after their launch
of L glutide which is a glp1 drug for
diabetes in the UK they have now signed
an exclusive license and Supply
agreement for the generic version of the
Blockbuster drug o zic which is
basically semaglutide with a Brazilian
company biom sa for Brazil now biocon
will undertake the development
manufacturing Supply biom will be
responsible for the regulatory approval
as well as commercialization remember
semaglutide is basically used as a u
used for diabetes it's a glp1 drug
Market size is $580 million in Brazil
but we all know the kind of traction
Nova nordis drug has got globally and
the entire segment of is expected to
probably touch hundred billion doar by
2028 so that's the kind of potential
that we're talking about or 2030
globally now the other one is jubilean
fova they have decided to close
manufacturing operations of their form
formulation facility in the US now their
subsidary in the US will continue sales
and marketing activities company has
indicated the extreme price pressure
that they faced in the faced in the US
resulted in sign ific losses in their
generics business in F22 onwards so
they're changing their model to in-house
manufacturing uh from in-house
manufacturing to an Outsource
Manufacturing in the US separately their
RI facility has received a VII so that
should help in terms of compensating
exports to the US uh overall they will
also look to sell off their land which
uh basically had the US facility so
that'll probably be probably take place
sometime later so that is something that
the street will watch out for expect
both these stocks to be in the green all
right
thank very much for that well uja cement
is the next one we want to focus on
sashan has got details on this one so
morning morning pan so promoter adani
family has completed the warrant
subscription and with this total fund
infusion in increases to rupes 20,000 CR
and holding of the promoter increases to
70.3% in the latest trans warrant worth
8,339 CR is subscribed earlier in
October 2022 promoter had infused 5,000
CR and in March 2024 for had infused
6,660 61 CR so what will this fund be
used for company says it will be
instrumental to achieve 140 million tons
per year capacity by 2028 and fund will
also enable strategic initiatives
including debot linking the capex
commenting on the same the CEO says fund
infusion provides Capital flexibility
for fast act growth Capital Management
initiatives and balance sheet
strength okay thanks for that well uh
let's go across to abishek now he's
going to track uh he's tracking IFL
Finance abishek why is that uh well IFL
Finance has announced a right issue uh
so for one share will be issued for
every nine shares that you held in the
company uh in terms of total fundr it's
close to about
1,272 crores uh which is being priced at
rupees 300 per share so this 300 per
share is at a discount of around 30% to
the CMP or last closing price of IFL
Finance calculation shows that Equity d
could be around the 11% level 11.1% to
be precise and CR that is capital
adequacy ratio that can increase by
2.25% to 2 and a half% depending on
where their rwa stands uh which will
lead to close to CR of 22% so this
fundraise would actually help them in
terms of controlling their cost of funds
we are is a rising interest rate
scenario until and unless the funds are
used for Provisions back to you all
right very helpful there thanks a lot
for that well let's do a quick recap in
case you missed out on any of these
stocks stocks with positive News St as
ICI lombar just dial Brigade Enterprises
suntech realy ambuja cement IFL finance
biocon jub and fova and Angel one while
the only stock on our radar with
negative news flow and of course because
of earnings is starta Communications but
let's also get a quick grip on what's
happening in the world of Commodities
because Brent crude after Rising for
many days has finally softened a bit uh
much to the relief of investors but
Manisha Gupta is here to give us a
Roundup of all of that Manisha morning
thank you for that Sonia well we had a
TR we but uh in the US markets yesterday
we did see crude oil prices decline by
3% so we are trading below 90 and 87 is
where we are resting right now the
reason for such sharp decline is the eia
report which is suggesting that the US
crud inventories have surged by 2.7
million barrels this is much higher than
what the street was anticipating but
then again uh there are reports about us
looking to reinstate oil sanctions on
Venezuela European Union is talking
about fresh curbs on Iran so these
factors will lead to some buying back
coming in case of fruit prices but the
only space that has continued to shine
bright has been the metal sector of
course the precious metals are doing
well but the ferris Metals the base
metals also seem to be surging fine
copper is trading half a percent on the
higher side right now aluminum prices
have surged to a 22 Monon highs and the
lards like ior are trading on the
positive side even the steel prices
formed up by 2% in early Asian markets
today the anticipation that demand is
improving better economic data from the
global manufacturing markets all of that
seems to be supported all right Manisha
thanks very much for that uh so you know
Commodities and metals have been uh
doing good and we'll track them uh this
morning as well we'll take a quick
commercial break here deep mea elor
equities will join in for some uh stock
specific commentary on the other side
stay tuned
[Music]